animeonhand.com 2014-11-23

# AnimeOnHand Privacy | Watch Anime Online & Mobile

This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. The privacy policy is applicable to the website, "animeonhand" 

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets us know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content. Advertising companies and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter personal information (eg e-mail address). You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you). To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
